{
    "subject": "resource/Yoshio_Nishina",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Satosh\u014d,_Okayama",
    "human_readable": "Yoshio Nishina was born in Satosh\u014d, Okayama.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8832359910011292,
            "question": "Where was Yoshio Nishina born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8619261384010315,
            "question": "When was Yoshio Nishina born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8475240468978882,
            "question": "In what city was Yoshio Nishina born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6190017461776733,
            "question": "What is Yoshio Nishina known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5724009275436401,
            "question": "Which country is Satosh\u014d, Okayama located in?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4977432191371918,
            "question": "Is there any information about Yoshio Nishina's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3599078357219696,
            "question": "What contributions did Yoshio Nishina make to science?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35263773798942566,
            "question": "Are there any institutions named after Yoshio Nishina?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3102050721645355,
            "question": "What significant events happened during Yoshio Nishina's lifetime?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.28753697872161865,
            "question": "Did Yoshio Nishina receive any awards or recognition for his work?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Yoshio Nishina was born in Satosh\u014d, Okayama.",
            "html": "dbpedia_7266_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What significant events happened during Yoshio Nishina's lifetime?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7266_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Are there any institutions named after Yoshio Nishina?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7266_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What contributions did Yoshio Nishina make to science?",
            "html": "dbpedia_7266_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_11.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_33.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_40.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_43.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_7266_55.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in JSON format:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple that Yoshio Nishina was born in Satosh\u014d, Okayama. This is confirmed by multiple documents (file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7266/re-ranker-msmarco/23.txt, file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7266/re-ranker-msmarco/15.txt, and file_path: /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_7266/re-ranker-msmarco/50.txt)."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThis response is based on the information provided in the documents, which state that Yoshio Nishina was born in Satosh\u014d, Okayama."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Very Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}